{
    "subject": "resource/Roger_O'Donnell",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1955-10-29",
    "human_readable": "Roger O'Donnell was born on October 29, 1955.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8964701294898987,
            "question": "When was Roger O'Donnell born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8141966462135315,
            "question": "What decade was Roger O'Donnell born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7709580063819885,
            "question": "Roger O'Donnell was born in the middle of what century?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7201269865036011,
            "question": "What month and day was Roger O'Donnell born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6656985282897949,
            "question": "What can you tell me about Roger O'Donnell's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6344196200370789,
            "question": "How old is Roger O'Donnell as of today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4884500503540039,
            "question": "In what year did Roger O'Donnell come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4800940155982971,
            "question": "Is Roger O'Donnell older than 60 years old?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3926301598548889,
            "question": "What is significant about October 29th?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3704182207584381,
            "question": "If today is November 1st, 2023, how many days have passed since Roger O'Donnell's birth?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Roger O'Donnell was born on October 29, 1955.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2608_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is significant about October 29th?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2608_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Roger O'Donnell older than 60 years old?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2608_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Roger O'Donnell come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2608_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2608_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents consistently provide information that supports the statement \"Roger O'Donnell was born on October 29, 1955.\" This is explicitly stated in multiple files."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}